Guide to the Mick Moloney Irish-American Music and Popular Culture Field Recordings AIA.031.002
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Public Performances, 1965-1997, Jun 25, 1965-Feb 22, 1997
  - Solas: Seamus Egan (flute, banjo, mandolin), Winifred Horan (fiddle), John Doyle (guitar), Karan Casey (vocals), John Williams (accordion). Concert performance at the Celtic Appalachian Celebration, International House, Philadelphia, PA. (One CD – Length: 00:38:26) aiamm188C, 1996; aiamm188C (Box 7, Folder 31, Box 10, Box 34)
  - Drinking: The Musical, Wayside Inn (David Ingle, Shelly Kellman, Libby Franck, Hall Kirkham). aiamm1295C, Feb 11, 1997; aiamm1295C (Box 65, Box 44)
  - Laurel Theater in Knoxville, TN. aiamm1341C, Feb 22, 1997; aiamm1341C (Box 44, Box 73)
  - Moloney, Mick, and Friends: Mick Moloney (banjo, vocals), Zan McLeod (guitar), Kieran O'Hare (uilleann pipes, whistle), Kathleen Keane (fiddle). Concert performance, Jubilee Community Arts at the Laurel Theatre, Knoxville, TN recorded by Lou Gross. (One CD – Length: 00:32:07) aiamm189C, Feb 22, 1997; aiamm189C (Box 34, Box 7, Folder 32, Box 10)
  - Moloney, Mick (vocals, guitar, banjo), Ivers, Eileen (fiddle), Keane, Jimmy (accordion) Concert performance in Gainesville, FL. (Length: 00:05:00). aiamm1121C, Mar 1, 1997; aiamm1121C (Box 41, Box 26)
  - Feast of Irish Folk. Irish radio show including interview with Shay Duffin, actor in one-man play, Behan. (Length: 01:30:00) aiamm1123C, Mar 16, 1998; aiamm1123C (Box 26, Box 61)
  - Feast of Irish Folk. "Day 4." Radio show on WHPK, Chicago featuring an interview with Pat Broaders (bouzouki, vocals). (Length: 01:30:00) aiamm1124C, May 4, 1998; aiamm1124C (Box 61, Box 26)
  - Elkins, WV: Labeled "3 Hornpipes." aiamm1452C, 1998; aiamm1452C (Box 44, Box 69)
  - Augusta Irish Week. Second half of a concert performance in Elkins, WV hosted by Mick Moloney. Musicians include: John Skelton (flute), Matt Shortridge (fiddle), Pauline Conneely (banjo), Bridget Fitzgerald (vocals), James Kelly (fiddle), Zan McLeod (bouzouki), Mark Stone (bodhran) (Length: 00:50:00) aiamm1127C, Jul 27, 1999; aiamm1127C (Box 61, Box 26)
  - Augusta Irish Week. Second half of a concert performance in Elkins, WV hosted by James Kelly. Musicians include: Brendan Callahan (fiddle), Jim Eagan (fiddle), Aran Olwell (flute), Matt Mulqueen (piano), Robbie O'Connell (vocals, guitar), Mick Moloney (vocals, banjo), Tommy Keane (uilleann pipes), Jacqueline McCarthy (concertina) (Length: 00:50:00) aiamm1128C, Jul 29,1999; aiamm1128C (Box 61, Box 26)
  - Augusta Irish Week. Second half of a concert performance in Elkins, WV. Musicians include: Mike Rafferty (flute), Mary Rafferty (accordion), Pauline Conneely (banjo),Ged Foley (guitar), Bridget Fitzgerald (vocals), Benedict Koehler and Kevin Rowsome (uilleann pipes), Joanie Madden (flute), Siobhan Egan (fiddle), Albert Alfonso (bodhran), Zan McLeod (bouzouki), Mick Mulkerin and Regan Wick (dance) (Length: 01:00:00) aiamm1122C, Jul, 1997; aiamm1122C (Box 61, Box 26)
  - Crowley, Jimmy (vocals, bouzouki); Mulcahy Family: Mick (accordion), Louise and Michelle (multiple instruments) Side A: Solo Crowley concert performance in Cork City. Moloney sits in on banjo; Side B: Mulcahy Family concert performance at Lake Hotel in Killarney featuring Q & A with Moloney at the end. (Total length: 01:30:00) aiamm1120C, 1997; aiamm1120C (Box 61, Box 26)
  - Augusta Irish Week. Concert performance by Robbie O'Connell (vocals, guitar) in Elkins, WV. (Length: 00:20:00) aiamm1126C, 1999; aiamm1126C (Box 61, Box 26)
  - Folkmasters. "Banjo Breakdown." Radio Smithsonian show from Woftrap hosted by Nick Spitzer featuring Mick Moloney and Seamus Egan (banjos). (Length: 01:00:00) aiamm1073C, 1990s; aiamm1073C (Box 26, Box 60)
  - Washington Square Ceili Band, NYU Irish Music Ensemble: Mick Moloney (Banjo and Mandolin) and Tony DiMarco (Fiddle). aiamm3CD, Spring 2000; aiamm3CD (Box 76, Box 79)
  - Augusta Irish Week, 20th Anniversary: Carroll, Liz; McComiskey, Billy; Moloney, Mick; McLeod, Zan; Long, Donna aiamm1303C, Jul 24, 2001; aiamm1303C (Box 44, Box 65)
  - Augusta Irish Week, 20th Anniversary: First Half of Concert aiamm1315C, Jul 24, 2001; aiamm1315C (Box 65, Box 44)
  - Augusta Irish Week, 20th Anniversary: Second Half of Concert. aiamm1487C, Jul 24, 2001; aiamm1487C (Box 72, Box 45)
  - Augusta Irish Week, 20th Anniversary. First half of a concert performance in Elkins, WV hosted by James Kelly. Musicians include: Karen Ashbrook (dulcimer), Paul Ortz (guitar), Brendan Callahan (fiddle), Jim Eagan (fiddle), Aran Olwell (flute), Matt Mulqueen (piano), Elliot Grasso (uilleann pipes), Jordan Dudney (dance), Frank Harte (vocals), Robbie O'Connell (vocals, guitar), Mick Moloney (vocals, banjo), Tommy Keane (uilleann pipes), Jacqueline McCarthy (concertina) (Length: 01:00:00) aiamm1129C, Jul 26, 2001; aiamm1129C (Box 26, Box 61)
  - Augusta Irish Week, 20th Anniversary. Second half of a concert performance in Elkins, WV hosted by James Kelly. Musicians include: Carol Thompson (harp), Mary O'Malley (poet), Marie Reilly (fiddle), Martin Reilly (accordion), Zan McLeod (bouzouki), Albert Alfonso (bodhran), Jordan Dudley (dance), Bill Maple, finale with Joanie Madden (flute), Billy McComiskey (accordion), Pauline Conneely (banjo), Robbie O'Connell (vocals, guitar), Mick Moloney (vocals, banjo) (Length: 01:20:00) aiamm1130C, Jul 26, 2001; aiamm1130C (Box 61, Box 26)
  - Augusta Irish Week, 20th Anniversary. Labeled "CD 2 of 2, 19 Tracks." aiamm21CD, 2001; aiamm21CD (Box 79, Box 76)
  - Augusta Irish Week: Jackie Daly. aiamm22CD, Jul 27, 2004; aiamm22CD (Box 79, Box 76)
  - Augusta Irish Week: Mick Moloney and Staff. aiamm20CD, Jul 25, 2006; aiamm20CD (Box 76, Box 79)
  - All Things Considered. Labeled "Irish Music #850420." NPR radio broadcast about the Ethnic Folk Arts Festival and the genesis of Cherish the Ladies featuring short interviews with Moloney, Liz Carroll and the teenaged Joanie Madden. (Length: 00:10:00). aiamm1133C, undated; aiamm1133C (Box 26, Box 41)
  - Side A: Anderson, Alistair; Side B: Dubliners. aiamm1366C, undated; aiamm1366C (Box 66, Box 44)
  - At the Bride. Radio show of a concert performance at the Painted Bride Arts Center in Philadelphia, PA. with interviews. Musicians: Mick Moloney (guitar, vocals, banjo), Jimmy Keane (accordion), Robbie O'Connell (vocals, guitar), Garnet Rogers (guitar, vocals). (Length: 00:30:00) aiamm1134C, undated; aiamm1134C (Box 26, Box 61)
  - Augusta Irish Week. John Whelan concert performance in Elkins, WV. Musicians include: Mick Moloney (vocals, banjo), John Whelan (accordion), Brian Conway (fiddle), Zan McLead (bouzouki), Mark Stone (bodhran), Michael Smith (Length: 00:20:00). aiamm1135C, undated; aiamm1135C (Box 41, Box 26)
  - "Ballad Workshops - 3rd Irish Music Festival - Part 2 of 2." aiamm539R, undated; aiamm539R (Box 19, Box 62)
  - Benford, Mac at New York University Skirball Center. aiamm1464C, undated; aiamm1464C (Box 45, Box 72)
  - "Best of Irish etc. Lowell - Reel 2." Concert performance by Green Fields of America in Lowell, MA. aiamm540R, undated; aiamm540R (Box 62, Box 23)
  - Boston Session. Session at Robert Geal's home with Paddy Cronin (fiddle). (Length: 00:45:00). aiamm1136C, undated; aiamm1136C (Box 26, Box 41)
  - "Ceili Music Concert - Wilkes Barre/Liz Carroll." aiamm1137C, undated; aiamm1137C (Box 27, Box 62)
  - "A Celebration of Irish/American Music", Southern Illinois University at Carbondale, 1997 (Box Shared Tamiment 030, Folder 19, Box 79, Cassette aiamm1506A - aiamm1506C)
  - "Celtic Roots" PRI Radio Smithsonian radio program, Folk Masters, featuring Moloney, Irish and Cape Breton music. (Length: 01:00:00). aiamm1138C, undated; aiamm1138C (Box 62, Box 26)
  - "Chicago House Session: McGreevy, Carroll, Jimmy and Eleanor Neary, Johnny Harding, Frank Burke - TAPE 4." aiamm542R, undated; aiamm542R (Box 19, Box 62)
  - "Chieftains." aiamm1141C, undated; aiamm1141C (Box 27, Box 62)
  - "Chieftains Live." aiamm1139C, undated; aiamm1139C (Box 27, Box 62)
  - Chieftains. Beginning of concert performance MCed by Moloney. Dupe with slightly more material. (Length: 01:20:00) aiamm1140C, undated; aiamm1140C (Box 62, Box 26)
  - "Concert at Wilkes Barre - Part II - Last Tune." aiamm1142C, undated; aiamm1142C (Box 27, Box 62)
  - Copy of Armin Barnett's Tape with Index: Frank George - fiddle, Pete Hoover - banjo, and Alan Jabbour play tunes in parking lot of a hotel, old time and Irish music. aiamm543R, undated; aiamm543R (Box 62, Box 19)
  - "Copy of Patrick Kane's tape - Martin O'Connor, Noel Hill etc." aiamm1143C, undated; aiamm1143C (Box 62, Box 27)
  - "Copy of Tape Made for Dick Shea." aiamm1144C, undated; aiamm1144C (Box 62, Box 27)
  - "Dan Milner/Seamus." aiamm1145C, undated; aiamm1145C (Box 62, Box 27)
  - DeDanann. Concert performance with chat between tunes edited out. (Length: 01:00:00) aiamm1225C, undated; aiamm1225C (Box 64, Box 26)
  - "Early American Recordings." Radio program on WHYY, Philadelphia, PA about the Ziegfield Follies and featuring Nora Bayes. (Length: 00:40:00) aiamm1146C, undated; aiamm1146C (Box 26, Box 62)
  - "Easter Rising – Kathleen's Show." Radio documentary about Irish oppression from a series called Penumbra. (Length: 00:30:00) aiamm1147C, undated; aiamm1147C (Box 62, Box 26)
  - English Folk Songs for "Class Use." Compilation of folk songs from the commercially released Folktrax series. (Length: 01:00:00) aiamm1148C, undated; aiamm1148C (Box 62, Box 26)
  - "First WCAM Program: Tony Campbell, Tony Palczar and Al Payne, Mary McHugh, Tommy Caulfield Jr." aiamm544R, undated; aiamm544R (Box 62, Box 19)
  - Flanagan Brothers. aiamm545R, undated; aiamm545R (Box 62, Box 16)
  - Gavin, Frankie (fiddle), Cahill, Eddie (flute), Moloney, Mick (banjo). Good small session (10 minutes) followed by DeDanaan with Johnny Moynihan in overmodulated concert at the Philadelphia Irish Festival. (Total length: 00:30:00). aiamm1149C, undated; aiamm1149C (Box 41, Box 26)
  - Georgetown Concert Sets. aiamm1247C, undated; aiamm1247C (Box 44, Box 68)
  - Germantown Session. House session with Mick Moloney, Chuck and Kathy O'Donnell, Lisa and Kit Healy, Timmy Britton, Carl Zuckerman, Dan Doherty. (Length: 01:00:00) aiamm546R, undated; aiamm546R (Box 55, Box 16)
  - "GFA Tape #11." aiamm547R, undated (Box 19)
  - Goodman, Steve: WXPN Tape. aiamm1384C, undated; aiamm1384C (Box 44, Box 69)
  - Green Fields of America. "GFA #19, SF Session #II." Noisy pub session in San Francisco, CA. Musicians include: Mick Moloney, Jack Coen (flute), unidentified accordion, concertina, pipes, bodhran, fiddle. (Length: 01:00:00) aiamm548R, undated; aiamm548R (Box 62, Box 16)
  - Green Fields of America. "GFA #21, SF Session #IV." Noisy pub session in San Francisco, CA. Musicians include: Mick Moloney, Jack Coen (flute), unidentified accordion, concertina, pipes, bodhran, fiddle. (Length: 01:00:00) aiamm549R, undated; aiamm549R (Box 61, Box 16)
  - Green Fields of America. "GFA #22, SF Session #V." Noisy pub session in San Francisco, CA. Musicians include: Mick Moloney, Jack Coen (flute), unidentified accordion, concertina, pipes, bodhran, fiddle. (Length: 01:00:00) aiamm550R, undated; aiamm550R (Box 61, Box 16)
  - Harrigan and Hart Compilation Created by Mick Moloney, undated; cuid36938 (Box Electronic Records, Item TW_AIA_031_002_ER_4)
  - International House Festival. "Sun. PM Workshop Area B - Irish Instrumental Music in America." Musiciand include Moloney, O'Donnell. aiamm551R, undated; aiamm551R (Box 19, Box 61)
  - International Village Fair. "Western European Day." Concert performances in Philadelphia, PA. Side A: Cape Breton musicians include: Maybelle Chisolm McQueen, Buddy MacMaster, David MacIsaacs, John Pellerin; Side B: Old Time musicians include: LeVon Robinson and the Fiddle Puppets dance troupe. (Length: 01:30:00) aiamm1150C, undated; aiamm1150C (Box 61, Box 26)
  - "Irish and Irish-American Music - Class Use." aiamm1152C, undated; aiamm1152C (Box 61, Box 27)
  - "Irish and Irish American Tunes and Songs for Class." Compilation of lace curtain and vaudeville commercial Irish 78s. (Length: 00:10:00). aiamm1151C, undated; aiamm1151C (Box 55, Box 26)
  - "Irish Music and Songs – Trends – Intro." Compilation of excerpts from commercial and field recordings with log. (Length: 00:30:00). aiamm1153C, undated; aiamm1153C (Box 61, Box 26)
  - Irish Music in America. Mick Moloney reads a history of Irish music in America with musical and interview excerpts from commercial recordings and his field recordings. (Length: 01:00:00). aiamm552R, undated; aiamm552R (Box 63, Box 16)
  - The Johnstons. aiamm1256C, undated; aiamm1256C (Box 44, Box 67)
  - Jubilo String Band featuring Mike Gallagher. Concert performance at the Tacoma Tap Room, Tacoma Pk, MD. (Length: 00:30:00). aiamm1154C, undated; aiamm1154C (Box 63, Box 26)
  - "Keane, O'Connell, Moloney at Godfrey Daniels - Tape Two." aiamm1155C, undated; aiamm1155C (Box 63, Box 27)
  - Dan Kelly: Pat Bradey's Experience at the 1893 World's Fair in Chicago (dubbed from Mark56 LP). aiamm1480C, undated; aiamm1480C (Box 72, Box 45)
  - Kelly, James (fiddle), O'Brien, Paddy (accordion), Sproule, Daithi (guitar) Audio letter from James Kelly to Moloney featuring a concert performance at the Brazen Head pub, Dublin. (Length: 00:30:00). aiamm1156C, undated; aiamm1156C (Box 63, Box 26)
  - Kennedy, Frankie (flute), Ni Mhaonaigh, Mairead (fiddle, vocals) Intimate concert performance from the founding members of Altan with unidentified bouzouki and harp. (Length: 00:30:00). aiamm1157C, undated; aiamm1157C (Box 26, Box 41)
  - Killen, Lou and Sally (Englisk folk singers and concertina) Side A: Concert performance at small venue for folklorists; Side B features a long monologue by Louis. (Length: 01:00:00). aiamm1158C, undated; aiamm1158C (Box 63, Box 26)
  - Kirshenblatt-Gimblett, Barbara: Lecture. aiamm1279C, undated; aiamm1279C (Box 68, Box 44)
  - Kirshenblatt-Gimblett, Barbara: Lecture on Ethnicity aiamm1288C, undated; aiamm1288C (Box 65, Box 44)
  - Kurtz, Jeremy (bass) and unidentified piano. Concert performance of airs and tunes including "McGlynn's Jigs." (Length 00:10:00) aiamm1159C, undated; aiamm1159C (Box 55, Box 26)
  - "Long Irish." aiamm553R, undated; aiamm553R (Box 63, Box 19)
  - "Long Irish." aiamm554R, undated; aiamm554R (Box 19, Box 63)
  - Long Note. Irish radio program hosted by Moloney about composer Ed Reavy with interviews and musical examples. (Length: 00:20:00). aiamm1160C, undated; aiamm1160C (Box 41, Box 26)
  - MacNamara, Josephine (dancer) Solo whistle medley for MacNamara's tap routine recorded on low-fi tape recorder. (Length: 00:05:00) aiamm692C, undated; aiamm692C (Box 25, Box 77)
  - Makem, Tommy (vocals, guitar, whistle) Excerpts of a concert performance in Los Angeles. Very poor sound. (Length: 00:30:00) aiamm1161C, undated; aiamm1161C (Box 62, Box 26)
  - "Martin Mulhaire for Long Note." aiamm555R, undated; aiamm555R (Box 62, Box 19)
  - Maureen Glynn School. aiamm1266C, undated; aiamm1266C (Box 68, Box 44)
  - McGlynn, Sean; McComiskey, Billy at Wendy Newtons aiamm1309C, undated; aiamm1309C (Box 65, Box 44)
  - McGovern, Betsy (guitar, mandolin), Flaherty, Patrick (vocals) Overmodulated recording of a concert performance. (Length: 01:00:00) aiamm1162C, undated; aiamm1162C (Box 62, Box 26)
  - McGrath, Denis (ballad singer) Concert performance at Cobh International Festival, Co Cork. (Length: 00:30:00) aiamm1163C, undated; aiamm1163C (Box 62, Box 26)
  - McMahon, Liam (on Television). aiamm1470C, undated; aiamm1470C (Box 45, Box 72)
  - "Merry Ballads." Irish Arts Center session featuring songs and Margaret Barry (banjo, vocals). (Length: 01:00:00) aiamm556R, undated; aiamm556R (Box 62, Box 23)
  - "Mick and Group. Live Reel 3." 8 track master. aiamm557R, undated; aiamm557R (Box 62, Box 23)
  - "Mick Cronin's Tape - Session NY with Johnny Cronin." aiamm1164C, undated; aiamm1164C (Box 62, Box 27)
  - "Mick Hickey Tape." aiamm1165C, undated; aiamm1165C (Box 27, Box 62)
  - "Middleton Folk Festival." aiamm1166C, undated; aiamm1166C (Box 62, Box 27)
  - "Mike Seeger." aiamm1167C, undated; aiamm1167C (Box 62, Box 27)
  - Moloney, Mick (guitar, banjo, mandolin, vocals), O'Donnell, Eugene (fiddle), Egan, Seamus (flute, banjo) Two concert performances: Hot Springs and Mitchell, South Dakota. (Length: 01:00:00) aiamm1174C, undated; aiamm1174C (Box 62, Box 26)
  - Moloney, Mick (guitar, vocals, banjo), O'Donnell, Eugene (fiddle), Egan, Seamus (flute, banjo) Concert performance at International House, Philadelphia, PA. with dancer, Regan Wick preceded by a performance of Yeats poetry to harp accompaniment. Poor sound quality. (Length: 01:00:00) aiamm1168C, undated; aiamm1168C (Box 62, Box 26)
  - Moloney, Mick (teacher) Moloney teaches a class on sean nos singing with guest Danny Doyle. (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1169C, undated; aiamm1169C (Box 62, Box 26)
  - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo), O'Connell, Robbie (vocals, guitar), Keane, Jimmy (accordion). "Side 3, side 4." End of a concert performance. Poor sound quality. (Length: 00:35:00) aiamm1170C, undated; aiamm1170C (Box 62, Box 26)
  - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo, guitar), Ivers, Eileen (fiddle), Sands, Tommy (guitar, vocals) Concert performance in Tucson, AZ. (Length: 01:30:00). aiamm1171C, undated; aiamm1171C (Box 41, Box 26)
  - Moloney, Mick (vocals, banjo, guitar), O'Donnell, Eugene (fiddle), Egan, Seamus (flute, banjo) Concert performance in Juneau, AK. (01:30:00) aiamm1172C, undated; aiamm1172C (Box 62, Box 26)
  - Moloney, Mick; Ivers, Eileen; Sands, Tommy for West Virginia Public Broadcasting's Mountain Stage. aiamm1300C, undated; aiamm1300C (Box 68, Box 44)
  - "Moloney, O'Donnell, Keane, O'Connell at Godfrey Daniels." aiamm1173C, undated; aiamm1173C (Box 62, Box 27)
  - Mount Airy Festival. aiamm1360C, undated; aiamm1360C (Box 44, Box 71)
  - Night Anatolia Ensemble (Zenska, Balalaiku, Voloshkytm and Johnny Roussos). aiamm1328C, Jul 31; aiamm1328C (Box 71, Box 44)
  - Northern Irish Jig Competition, New York City. aiamm1285C, undated; aiamm1285C (Box 44, Box 72)
  - "O'Brien, O'Driscoll, Moloney, Egan Philadelphia Session." aiamm1175C, undated; aiamm1175C (Box 62, Box 27)
  - "Old-Time Back-Up Guitar Sample Tape." aiamm1329C, undated; aiamm1329C (Box 71, Box 44)
  - Ormond Star Ceile Band, "The Grand March" at Irish Dance Music Festival, undated; cuid36937 (Box Electronic Records, Item TW_AIA_031_002_ER_3)
  - Ó Tuathaigh, Gearóid: Lecture on British Colonial Policy. aiamm1370C, undated; aiamm1370C (Box 71, Box 44)
  - Ó Tuathaigh, Gearóid: Lecture on British Colonial Period. aiamm1461C, undated; aiamm1461C (Box 45, Box 69)
  - "Owen Hunt - Tunes for Tape." aiamm1176C, undated; aiamm1176C (Box 62, Box 27)
  - "Owen Hunt Collection." aiamm558R, undated; aiamm558R (Box 19, Box 63)
  - "Owen Hunt Tapes." aiamm560R, undated; aiamm560R (Box 20, Box 63)
  - "Owen Hunt Tapes. Lecture." aiamm559R, undated; aiamm559R (Box 63, Box 19)
  - "Owen Hunt Tapes. McPeakes, Lectures on Celts, History of Sligo, Banjo Mandolin, Later Paddy O'Brien." aiamm561R, undated; aiamm561R (Box 19, Box 63)
  - "Padraig O'Keefe I & II." Irish radio programs produced by Peter Browne about O'Keefe (fiddle) featuring music and interviews. See 178C. (Length: 01:30:00) aiamm1177C, undated; aiamm1177C (Box 63, Box 26)
  - "Padraig O'Keefe III & IV." Irish radio programs produced by Peter Browne about O'Keefe (fiddle) featuring music and interviews. See 177C. (Length: 01:30:00) aiamm1178C, undated; aiamm1178C (Box 26, Box 63)
  - Patchwork. New Jersey radio show hosted by Sandy Lewis featuring an interview with and stories from Jim Albertson. (Length: 00:45:00) aiamm1179C, undated; aiamm1179C (Box 63, Box 26)
  - Philadelphia Ceili Group Festival. "Evening Concert: Keane et. Al. cont'd., Connolly/Mulhaire, Touchstone." aiamm1180C, undated; aiamm1180C (Box 27, Box 63)
  - "Philadelphia Folk Festival." aiamm1132C, Aug 24; aiamm1132C (Box 61, Box 27)
  - Philadelphia Session. House session labeled "John Vesey, Tommy Caulfield, Ed Reavy, John Dogherty, M Moloney and Sundry Messers" including informal chat. (Length: 01:30:00). aiamm1181C, undated; aiamm1181C (Box 41, Box 26)
  - "Program on the Wren." aiamm1182C, undated; aiamm1182C (Box 27, Box 55)
  - Radio Tiperrary. Irish radio program featuring interview with 90-year old Sheila Stapleton (singer). (Length: 00:30:00) aiamm1183C, undated; aiamm1183C (Box 26, Box 63)
  - "Reynolds, B Mulvihill, McGlynn, Roger Sherlock Remixes, Burke Banjo." aiamm1184C, undated; aiamm1184C (Box 27, Box 55)
  - RTE Banjo Lecture: Tunes Only. aiamm1373C, undated; aiamm1373C (Box 71, Box 44)
  - Sands, Tommy and Colm (vocals, guitar) Poor recording of concert performance in Belfast featuring "Humpty Dumpty Was Pushed." (60 minutes); Robbie O'Connell demos of three songs (10 minutes) (Total length: 01:10:00) aiamm1185C, undated; aiamm1185C (Box 26, Box 63)
  - "Script: Ed Reavy's Fancy." aiamm562R, undated; aiamm562R (Box 63, Box 19)
  - "Sean McGlynn, Jimmy Kelly (Boston) from Jimmy Kelly's tape (Albany)." aiamm1186C, undated; aiamm1186C (Box 27, Box 63)
  - "Session: Sean O'Driscoll, P. O'Brien, S. Egan, Moloney." aiamm1192C, undated; aiamm1192C (Box 27, Box 63)
  - Session and Fiddlers. Kitchen session with Moloney (mandolin) and L. E. McCullogh (whistle) (5 minutes); unaccompanied private performance from Paddy Cronin (fiddle) (5 minutes); private performance from Eugene O'Donnell (fiddle) and Moloney (mandolin) (5 minutes); private performance and informal interview with Tommy Caulfield (fiddle) about the tunes and dancing (25 minutes). (Total length: 00:40:00). aiamm1187C, undated; aiamm1187C (Box 26, Box 41)
  - Session at Central Hotel, Miltown. Nice flute session that turns into another nice session with fiddles in Miltown Malbay, Co. Clare. (Length: 00:55:00) aiamm1188C, undated; aiamm1188C (Box 63, Box 26)
  - "Session at Jimmy Kelly's - Boston." aiamm1189C, undated; aiamm1189C (Box 27, Box 63)
  - Session at McGann's, Doolin/Session at the Ferryman. Two great pub sessions probably not recorded by Moloney. Side A: banjo, pipes, guitar, fiddle; Side B: American man says, "Friday night at the Ferryman with Siobhan Peoples and unidentified banjo." (Length: 01:00:00) aiamm1190C, undated; aiamm1190C (Box 63, Box 26)
  - "Session at Mike Leonard's House." aiamm1191C, undated; aiamm1191C (Box 27, Box 63)
  - "Short Irish." aiamm563R, undated; aiamm563R (Box 63, Box 19)
  - "Session on Sunday Night 1 Aug and Sean Corcoran (The Mice Are At It Again)." aiamm1131C, Aug 1; aiamm1131C (Box 27, Box 61)
  - "Sessions: Greally's, Miltown et.al." aiamm1193C, undated; aiamm1193C (Box 63, Box 27)
  - Singing Style Lecture. aiamm1262C, undated; aiamm1262C (Box 66, Box 44)
  - Smithsonian Lecture. Excerpts of commercial Irish recordings. (Length: 00:40:00) aiamm1194C, undated; aiamm1194C (Box 26, Box 63)
  - "Songs of 1916. Lecture ACIS." Compilation of rebel song commercial recordings from the 1960s. (Length: 00:20:00) aiamm1195C, undated; aiamm1195C (Box 63, Box 26)
  - "Songs to Learn." aiamm1264C, undated; aiamm1264C (Box 44, Box 65)
  - Sounds Traditional. Two radio programs from Ireland: Show 1: Remastered recordings "from the archives" including Seamus Ennis, Paddy Killoran. Show 2: Old traditional recordings including the Ed Reavy story. (Length: 01:30:00) aiamm1196C, undated; aiamm1196C (Box 63, Box 26)
  - "Sun PM - Uilleann Pipes Workshop: Ochs, Britton, McCullough - Lengthy Discussion on History, Construction, Styles of the Pipes, Ukranian Embroidery." aiamm564R, undated; aiamm564R (Box 63, Box 19)